<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aswin Manohar</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>this is my personal site</description><atom:link href="https://example.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2023 &lt;a href="mailto:aswinbio@gmail.com"&gt;Aswin Manohar&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 12:30:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>About me</title><link>https://example.com/posts/about-me/</link><dc:creator>Aswin Manohar</dc:creator><description>&lt;img alt="/images/FB_IMG_1600395812568.jpg" src="https://example.com/images/FB_IMG_1600395812568.jpg"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my slightly off-kilter corner of the internet!  As an data scientist with a passion for climate change solutions, I spend my days analyzing and interpreting data from satellites and other sources to develop AI based sustainability powering solutions to save the planet. But when I'm not saving the world or peering into latest data projects, you'll likely find me cozied up on the couch, enjoying a good movie (preferably with a beer) or brainstorming for a new idea (can be anything, don't judge you little shit).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, when I'm not glued to my computer screen, you'll likely find me in the kitchen, whipping up something delicious or not. On this website, you'll find my musings on everything from data science, AI, climate tech to life hacks, intense randomness, opinions you did not ask for, and, of course, quick recipes (for personal use) and movie reviews.  Oh, and did I mention that I'm also a master of telling jokes that no one seems to laugh at? It's a special talent, really. So come for the articles, stay for the food, and brace yourself for some cringe-worthy jokes!&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid>https://example.com/posts/about-me/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 10:14:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>